Inventory of the William J. Donovan Memorial Foundation records
Hoover Institution Archives
- Account statements and related correspondence, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 35: 5-6)
- Tax returns and related correspondence, 1996 (Box-folder 35: 7)
- Columbia University correspondence, 1995-1999 (Box-folder 36: 1-6)
- Miscellaneous correspondence and notes, 1995 (Box-folder 36: 7-8)
- Donovan Fellowships announcement, 1999 (Box-folder 36: 9)
- Framed portraits of William J. Donovan, 1991 (Box-folder 37: 1-4)
- Framed portraits of William J. Donovan, 1991 (Box-folder 38: 1-4)
- Paperweights with a medallion of William J. Donovan, 1990 (Box-folder 39: 1-3)
- Plaque relating to statue of William J. Donovan, 1988 (Box-folder 39: 4)
- Presentation box for medal, undated (Box-folder 39: 5)
- Medal for William J. Donovan award, 1990 (Box-folder 39: 6)
- Framed portrait of William J. Donovan, 1991 (Box-folder 39: 7)
- Program for exhibit, "With the Fighting Sixty-Ninth: Donovan in World War I,", 1986 (Box-folder 40: 1)
- Program for dedication of statue, 1988 (Box-folder 40: 2)
- Letters from Lisa Anderson, 1999 (Box-folder 40: 3)
- Serial issue, SIPA News, 1999 (Box-folder 40: 4)
- Brochure relating to Columbia University, School of International and Public Affairs, 1999 (Box-folder 40: 5)
- "The Clandestine War in Europe (1942-1945)," remarks of William J. Casey on receipt of the William J. Donovan Award, 1974 (Box-folder 40: 6)
- Framed portrait of William J. Donovan, 1991 (Box-folder 40: 7)
- Minutes of meetings of Board of Directors, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 41: 1)
- List of donors and minutes of meeting of Board of Directors, 1986 (Box-folder 41: 2)
- Notice of annual membership meeting, 1987 (Box-folder 41: 3)
- Agenda and minutes of meetings of Board of Directors, 1987 (Box-folder 41: 4)
- Minutes of meetings of Board of Directors, 1988 (Box-folder 41: 5-6)
- Agendas and proxies for annual membership meetings, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 41: 7-8)
- Agenda and notes for Board of Directors meeting, 1989 (Box-folder 41: 9-10)
- Floor plans for new office, 1998 (Box-folder 41: 11)
- Foundation brochure and miscellaneous correspondence, 1998 (Box-folder 41: 12)
- Budget for new office, 1998 (Box-folder 41: 13)
- Invoices, 1998 (Box-folder 41: 14)
- Correspondence regarding transfer of medals, 1998 (Box-folder 41: 15)
- Minutes of organizational meeting of Board of Directors, 1981 (Box-folder 42: 1)
- Agenda and correspondence relating to Board of Directors meeting, 1982 (Box-folder 42: 2)
- Minutes of meetings of Board of Directors, 1982 (Box-folder 42: 3-4)
- Budget, 1982 (Box-folder 42: 5)
- Agenda for meeting of Board of Directors, 1983 (Box-folder 42: 6)
- Minutes of meeting of Board of Directors, 1983 (Box-folder 42: 7)
- Financial report and statement, 1983 (Box-folder 42: 8)
- Minutes of meeting of Board of Directors, 1984 (Box-folder 42: 9)
- Lists of donors, 1983 (Box-folder 42: 10)
- Donovan Award Committee correspondence, 1991-1995 (Box-folder 43: 1-6)
- Agendas, minutes, and proxies relating to annual membership meetings, 1983-1992 (Box-folder 43: 7-13)
- Agendas, minutes, and notes relating to Board of Directors meetings, 1982 (Box-folder 43: 14-17)
- Correspondence, exhibit texts, reports, and resolutions relating to proposed National Historical Intelligence Museum (NHIM), undated (Box-folder 44: 1-4)
- Transcript of Senate hearing on proposed NHIM, 1983 (Box-folder 44: 5)
- Senate resolution on proposed NHIM, 1983 (Box-folder 44: 6)
- Position paper relating to Foundation's work with NHIM, 1982 (Box-folder 44: 7)
- Correspondence and notes relating to Martin Cramer and proposed NHIM, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 44: 8-11)
- Proposals relating to NHIM, 1983 (Box-folder 44: 12)
- Speeches from Donovan statue ceremony, 1988 (Box-folder 44: 13)
- Correspondence and résumé relating to OSS/Donovan symposium, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 44: 14)
- Miscellaneous correspondence, 1985 (Box-folder 44: 15)
- Invitations and programs relating to William J. Donovan Award dinners, 1979-1993 (Box-folder 45: 1)
- Presentation box for Donovan Award medal, 1993 (Box-folder 45: 2)
- Fundraising appeal letter and envelopes, 1996 (Box-folder 45: 3)
- Charter patron certificate, 1984 (Box-folder 45: 4)
- Budget for Donovan Fellowships, 1994 (Box-folder 46: 1)
- Proposal and announcement for Donovan Fellowships, 1995 (Box-folder 46: 2)
- Correspondence relating to Donovan Fellowships, 1995 (Box-folder 46: 3)
- General announcement and budget, 1993 (Box-folder 46: 4)
- Miscellaneous, 1996 (Box-folder 46: 5)
- Proposals, correspondence, and printed matter relating to intelligence education, 1982-1985 (Box-folder 46: 6-8)
- Correspondence and mailing to members, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 47: 1-2)
- Foundation brochures and update notices, 1983 (Box-folder 47: 3)
- Reprints of Senate hearing on proposed National Historical Intelligence Museum, 1983 (Box-folder 47: 4)
- Account statements, 1987 (Box-folder 48: 1-2)
- Invoices, 1987 (Box-folder 48: 3)
- Correspondence and synopsis relating to Donovan Fellowships, 1995 (Box-folder 48: 4-5)
- Miscellaneous correspondence and clippings, 1985-1996 (Box-folder 48: 6)
- Correspondence and announcement relating to Donovan Fellowships, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 48: 7)
- Letter to members, 1996 (Box-folder 48: 8)
- Report and lists of donations, 1997 (Box-folder 48: 9)
- Invoices, 1988 (Box-folder 49: 1)
- Correspondence and tax return, 1988 (Box-folder 49: 2)
- Invoices, 1989 (Box-folder 49: 3)
- Account statements, 1989 (Box-folder 49: 4)
- Tax return, 1989 (Box-folder 49: 5)
- Account statements, 1990 (Box-folder 49: 6)
- Invoices, 1990 (Box-folder 49: 7)
- Tax return, 1991 (Box-folder 49: 8)
- Account statements, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 50: 1)
- Tax returns, 1981-1990 (Box-folder 50: 2-7)
- Invoices, 1992 (Box-folder 50: 8)
- Account statements, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 51: 1)
- Deposit slips, 1991 (Box-folder 51: 2)
- Invoices, 1991 (Box-folder 51: 3)
- Tax returns, 1989-1991 (Box-folder 51: 4)